

Hán Hồng Sơn REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER

### OBJECTIVE -

I am Han Hong Son, a third-year student at Greenwich University. Short-term goals: Gain practical work experience, further develop knowledge in Android application programming, contribute to the company's current project, and complete my personal project during the implementation phase. Long-term goals: Conduct in-depth research on Android and iOS application development, and manage large projects with more than five team members.

## PROFILE -







Phung Khoang, Trung Van, Nam Tu Liem, Ha Noi

### SKILLS -

REACT NATIVE FIREBASE REDUX TYPESCRIPT JAVASCRIPT NODEJS

# REFERENCES

WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER**

1/2023 - 5/2023

#### TRI NGHIA TECHNOLOGY

#### Main responsibilities:

- Develop mobile applications using React Native
- · Design mobile application interfaces
- Integrate APIs for data handling in mobile applications
- Test mobile applications and provide feedback on bugs

#### **INTERN WEB DEVELOPER**

8/2023 - 10/2023

## FPT Software |Intern web developer

#### Main responsibilities:

- I was trained in web front-end programming from basic to advanced.
- I was involved in an e-commerce project using React.
- I experienced the culture and strict working process of F-soft.

## **REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER**

5/2024 - 8/2024

## **VMO Holdings**

## Main responsibilities:

- Develop mobile applications using React Native
- · Design mobile application interfaces
- Implement mobile application interfaces
- Integrate APIs for data handling in mobile applications

#### **EDUCATION** -

### INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

2019 - 2023

#### **GREENWICH UNIVERSITY**

Graduate with First Class Honours.

## PROJECTS -

## **DEVELOPER**

LMNX EDU 1/2023 - 5/2023

Name of customer LMNX Education

Your team size 3

### **Technologies**

React Native, NodeJs, PostGreSQL, Angular

#### Link

;&pli=

#### **DEVELOPER**

TASK HELPER 6/2024 - 8/2024

Name of customer VMA

Your Team Size 2

## **Technologies**

React native, Firebase, render, Stream SDK, NodeJs

#### ink

